1. waitForPageLoad(0)
5. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Object Repository/NacacStudentApp/HomePageElements/EventsHomePage"), 0)
9. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/NacacStudentApp/HomePageElements/EventsHomePage"))
13. waitForPageLoad(0)
17. delay(3)
21. println(getUrl())
25. println(studenturl + "events")
29. com.CommonUtilities.Verifications.VerifyTextMatch(getUrl(), studenturl + "events", "When click Events top nav the Events page not opened")
33. com.CommonUtilities.Verifications.VerifyElementPresentAndStopExecutionIfFailed(findTestObject("Object Repository/NacacStudentApp/Events/WithSupportFromHeader"), "Sponsers header is not shown in events page")
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/NacacStudentApp/HomePageElements/VideosButtonInTopNav"))
41. waitForPageLoad(0)
45. com.CommonUtilities.Verifications.VerifyTextMatch(getUrl(), studenturl + "videos", "When click Videos top nav the Events page not opened")
49. com.CommonUtilities.Verifications.VerifyElementPresentAndStopExecutionIfFailed(findTestObject("Object Repository/NacacStudentApp/Videos/ExploreVideosHeader"), "Explore Videos header is not shown in Videos page")
53. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/NacacStudentApp/HomePageElements/FavoritesInTopNav"))
57. waitForPageLoad(0)
61. com.CommonUtilities.Verifications.VerifyTextMatch(getUrl(), studenturl + "favorites", "When click Favorites top nav the favorites page not opened")
65. com.CommonUtilities.Verifications.VerifyElementPresentAndStopExecutionIfFailed(findTestObject("Object Repository/NacacStudentApp/HomePageElements/FavoriteHeaderInFavoritesPage"), "Favorites header is not shown in Favorites page")
69. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/NacacStudentApp/HomePageElements/ItinearariesTopNav"))
73. waitForPageLoad(0)
77. com.CommonUtilities.Verifications.VerifyTextMatch(getUrl(), studenturl + "itineraries?activeTab=0", "When click My Schedule top nav the page is not opened")